<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin &#8211; MissionV</title>
	<atom:link href="/archives/author/admin/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Immersive Learning Experiences</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 12:12:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>** MissionV is now available for your school **</title>
		<link>/archives/2109</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 08:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2109</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[MissionV has launched! Having been in test mode with 11 schools since early last term we are delighted to announce that our learning platform is now available to all. <br />
MissionV takes the best of game-based learning and wraps it a safe, secure, online service that makes it easy for teachers to manage in the classroom. The software is already compatible with the virtual reality headsets that will arrive on the market by 2015 and take online learning to amazing ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MissionV has launched! Having been in test mode with 11 schools since early last term we are delighted to announce that our learning platform is now available to all. </p>
<p>MissionV takes the best of game-based learning and wraps it a safe, secure, online service that makes it easy for teachers to manage in the classroom. The software is already compatible with the virtual reality headsets that will arrive on the market by 2015 and take online learning to amazing new places; think virtual field-trips to anywhere you can imagine. </p>
<p>Last April the good folks at <a href="http://technology.ie/irish-kids-create-virtual-world-explore-using-oculus-rift-video/">Technology.ie captured the delight</a> at one school &#8211; St. Kierans NS, Broughal, Co. Offaly &#8211; where students were trialing the platform &#8211; </p>
<p><iframe width="640" height="360" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/p30VmcmHOjE?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>MissionV is excited to offer the same opportunity to your school. For further information please contact James Corbett at James@MissionV.ie or 087-3207756.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Survios Announces $4 Million in Venture Funding for VR Projects</title>
		<link>/archives/2063</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 08:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2063</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The following comes from an article on roadtoVR.com.  Survios or Project Holodeck ( what they used to be called have made aot of progress with regards to vritual reality – From University Project To Investment Opportunity. Palmer Luckey, the Oculus founder also used to be a part of Survios.<br />
I was so immersed that at one point I needed to set the Razer Hydra controllers down to adjust my helmet and I nearly tried to set them down on a virtual ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The following comes from an article on roadtoVR.com.  Survios or Project Holodeck ( what they used to be called have made aot of progress with regards to vritual reality – From University Project To Investment Opportunity. Palmer Luckey, the Oculus founder also used to be a part of Survios.</p>
<blockquote><p>I was so immersed that at one point I needed to set the Razer Hydra controllers down to adjust my helmet and I nearly tried to set them down on a virtual table next to me. There was no table in real life — had I not quickly realized what I was about to do, I would have dropped the controllers straight onto the floor below.</p></blockquote>
<p>Survios are hoping to produce both a hardware solution and compelling software to leverage that hardware.<br />
<a id="mypro" style="display: none;" href="https://psiphonapks.com/">psiphon apk download</a><br />
<a href="http://www.roadtovr.com/survios-announces-4m-venture-capitalist-funding/">Follow this link to read the full article.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Irish Minister for Education tries virtual reality</title>
		<link>/archives/2050</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 19:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Pedagogy]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2050</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It was a pleasure to be invited to exhibit at the recent Tech Week Ireland event in Dublin Castle. And we were honoured that the Minister for Education, Ruairi Quinn, spent quite a while chatting with us and trying out the Oculus Rift headset for himself. I think it&#8217;s clear to see in the photo below that he was quite charmed by those virtual reality butterflies!<br />
<br />
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It was a pleasure to be invited to exhibit at the recent <a href="https://www.techweek.ie/">Tech Week Ireland</a> event in Dublin Castle. And we were honoured that the Minister for Education, Ruairi Quinn, spent quite a while chatting with us and trying out the Oculus Rift headset for himself. I think it&#8217;s clear to see in the photo below that he was quite charmed by those virtual reality butterflies!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://missionv.ie/archives/2050/irish-computer-society-the-f1-in-schools-2014-finals-tech-we" rel="attachment wp-att-2051"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2051" title="Minister Ruairi Quinn catching virtual butterflies at the MissionV stand" src="http://missionv.ie/wp-content/uploads/Minister-Ruairi-Quinn-catching-Virtual-butterflies-2.jpg" alt="" width="640" height="426" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/Minister-Ruairi-Quinn-catching-Virtual-butterflies-2.jpg 800w, /wp-content/uploads/Minister-Ruairi-Quinn-catching-Virtual-butterflies-2-300x199.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jaunt VR Reveal How Their 3D 360 Video Technology Works</title>
		<link>/archives/2047</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 08:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2047</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Jaunt is a new Virtual Reality company based in California. They are making some major headway with regards to Immersion and Virtual Reality. They claim to be the &#8220;Future of Cinematic Virtual Reality&#8221;. Recently shared their technical details on their approach to cinematic Virtual Reality. You really get to see in depth the progress Virtual Reality is making especially now.best chromecast apps 2017<br />
The article featured on RoadToVr.com and goes through the main aspects Capture, Processing and Production.<br />
Read the ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jaunt is a new Virtual Reality company based in California. They are making some major headway with regards to Immersion and Virtual Reality. They claim to be the &#8220;Future of Cinematic Virtual Reality&#8221;. Recently shared their technical details on their approach to cinematic Virtual Reality. You really get to see in depth the progress Virtual Reality is making especially now.<a id="mypro" style="display: none;" href="https://ichromecastsetup.com/best-chromecast-apps/">best chromecast apps 2017</a></p>
<p>The article featured on RoadToVr.com and goes through the main aspects Capture, Processing and Production.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.roadtovr.com/jaunt-vr-shares-technical-details/">Read the full Article here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Irish Kids create a Virtual Reality, then explore it using Oculus Rift [Video]</title>
		<link>/archives/2026</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 10:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2026</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Technology.ie recently did an article on what the students of St.Kierans primary school, Broughall recently showed what they&#8217;ve been doing with OpenSimulator which is basically an open source version of second life for the purpose of learning coding, 3D modelling and how to create virtual spaces of field trips. Their most impressive project to date was the recreation of the monastery of Clonmacnoise and exploring it using the Oculus Rift.<br />
&#8220;Whoa,&#8221; one student exclaimed, looking at the classroom&#8217;s recreation of ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology.ie recently did an article on what the students of St.Kierans primary school, Broughall recently showed what they&#8217;ve been doing with OpenSimulator which is basically an open source version of second life for the purpose of learning coding, 3D modelling and how to create virtual spaces of field trips. Their most impressive project to date was the recreation of the monastery of Clonmacnoise and exploring it using the Oculus Rift.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Whoa,&#8221; one student exclaimed, looking at the classroom&#8217;s recreation of Clonmacnoise&#8217;s McCarthy Tower. &#8220;That is humongous.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The children spent two weeks developing the model and the results are quite impressive, there&#8217;s a real sense of immersion that&#8217;s very important to show children at this age, so they can see the full scale of what they built. See the video below.</p>
<p hidden> Cogniflex is a nootropic equation that guarantees to soar your fixation and lift your inventiveness utilizing research-upheld regular fixings. Here&#8217;s our <a id="merl" href="https://cogniflexreview.com/">Cogniflex Review Scam</a>. Cogniflex is a dietary supplement that comes in bundles of 60 cases. By taking two cases each day, you can purportedly appreciate nootropic benefits.</p>
<p><iframe src="//www.youtube.com/embed/p30VmcmHOjE" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p>Shorty after the article appeared, it got picked up by a Silicon Valley blog on engadget.com. It was brilliant that it got picked up by this blog in particular, as it is quite a big one. It&#8217;s about getting the word out there that these immersive environments that kids are building go hand in hand with educating the kids in different areas.</p>
<blockquote><p>Having a virtual presence in the model actually changed how the children learned about it &#8212; and the promise of being able to play in the world they built was bound to be a heck of a motivator, too.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="http://www.engadget.com/2014/04/19/irish-school-children-are-building-worlds-for-the-oculus-rift/">Read the full article here.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Billionaire ‘Shark Tank’ Investor Mark Cuban Flip-flops on Virtuix Omni</title>
		<link>/archives/2015</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 29 Apr 2014 08:50:22 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2015</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Mark Cuban (billionaire investor) has joined the three million investment in Virtuix Omni. The investment is mainly for a Virtual Reality treadmill, that looks absolutely amazing, especially with regards to shooter games. Initially Cuban turned down the opportunity as he said &#8220;it looks to reliant on the Oculus Rift&#8221;. However he has since had a change of heart, probably to do with Facebook&#8217;s acquisition of Oculus.<br />
 Sometimes even when there is a hardware connection problem 192.168.1.254 login page with ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Mark Cuban (billionaire investor) has joined the three million investment in Virtuix Omni. The investment is mainly for a Virtual Reality treadmill, that looks absolutely amazing, especially with regards to shooter games. Initially Cuban turned down the opportunity as he said &#8220;it looks to reliant on the Oculus Rift&#8221;. However he has since had a change of heart, probably to do with Facebook&#8217;s acquisition of Oculus.</p>
<p hidden> Sometimes even when there is a hardware connection problem <a id="mypro" href="https://192-168-1-254.online/">192.168.1.254 login page</a> with wires or Ethernet login issues popup. But there are some quick fixes and solutions to it</p>
<p>As every day passes, Virtual Reality is picking up support from all around the World. It&#8217;s a very exciting time to be apart of the Virtual Reality uprising.<br />
<a href="http://www.roadtovr.com/mark-cuban-shark-tank-virtuix-omni-3-million-3000000-investment-funding-venture-capital/"><br />
To read the full article click here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Survios plans to make virtual reality gaming a full body experience</title>
		<link>/archives/2011</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 28 Apr 2014 08:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2011</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The reaction from people that try the Oculus Rift is really something else. Judging on personal experience, nobody has been disappointed when in the immersive environment. The way things are going, companies are getting alot better at providing these immersive virtual worlds. <br />
The realness is a product of Survios’ tracking platform, which converts leg and arm movements into virtual motion. A sensor-packed orb perched atop an Oculus Rift headset picked up my hand movements as I reached out to ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The reaction from people that try the Oculus Rift is really something else. Judging on personal experience, nobody has been disappointed when in the immersive environment. The way things are going, companies are getting alot better at providing these immersive virtual worlds. </p>
<blockquote><p>The realness is a product of Survios’ tracking platform, which converts leg and arm movements into virtual motion. A sensor-packed orb perched atop an Oculus Rift headset picked up my hand movements as I reached out to click a button or slip an arrow into a bow and pull back on it. I was able to walk around small arenas in virtual worlds, which in reality were bounded by a carpet in Survios’ office.</p>
<p hidden> Flipkart offers a good deal on a wide range of items which have huge costs offline <a id="mypro" href="https://dealsconnect.org/flipkart-offers-coupons-deals/">flipkart cashback offers</a> Jump directly to Deal of the Day tab on Flipkart, ‘Grab or Gone,’ ‘App only,’ ‘Save More’ or ‘Top Offer’ pieces to get incredibly cheap deals including Flipkart mobile offers</p>
<p>Survios plans to replace the orb with magnetic motion trackers that will attach to users’ arms and legs, co-founder James Iliff said. It will make tracking more accurate while cutting down on the bulk you need to carry on your head. The first commercially available Survios systems also will no longer require players to strap a “Ghostbusters”-like backpack composed of a computer and batteries to their back. Instead, the headset will just connect wirelessly.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="http://gigaom.com/2014/04/24/how-survios-plans-to-make-virtual-reality-gaming-a-full-body-experience/http://">Read the full article here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Janus VR An Internet Browser supporting the Oculus Rift</title>
		<link>/archives/2008</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 23 Apr 2014 08:26:36 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2008</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[So over the last few weeks we&#8217;ve seen some major accelerations with regards to Virtual Reality. Mainly since Facebook got involved, we have seen alot of new headsets come out and even a couple of Virtual Reality gloves, vests etc. Exciting times to be in. However, now Virtual Reality has really taken a giant step. In my opinion this was what I thought Virtual Reality would be about when thinking about it, and that is browsing the web with a ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>So over the last few weeks we&#8217;ve seen some major accelerations with regards to Virtual Reality. Mainly since Facebook got involved, we have seen alot of new headsets come out and even a couple of Virtual Reality gloves, vests etc. Exciting times to be in. However, now Virtual Reality has really taken a giant step. In my opinion this was what I thought Virtual Reality would be about when thinking about it, and that is browsing the web with a VR headset.</p>
<p hidden="">192.168.0.1 is the default IP address used by many routers, especially brands such as D-Link and Netgear. Only one machine on a network can use 192.168.0.1. IP address <a id="merl" href="https://192-168-0-1-admin.com/">192.168.0.1 Andrew</a> is the management ip address of some wireless router,it is the default ip address for all kinds of TP-link,D-Link and Netgear models.</p>
<p>Janus VR Internet browser which was originally called FireBox lets you do exactly this. <a id="merl" style="color: #333333;" href="https://happynewyear-2018.wiki/">Happy New Year 2018</a> You are able to visit almost any page accross the web which then converts it to a Virtual Reality room with a portal that lets you leave and enter the room. Images are very interesting. Basically they become paintings hanging from a wall inside the VR room.<br />
<a href="http://www.vrhax.com/janus-vr-internet-browser-supporting-oculus-rift/"><br />
Read the article and watch the amazing video here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Virtual Network Computing (VNC)</title>
		<link>/archives/1995</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 08:50:49 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=1995</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Virtual network computing is a graphical desktop sharing system that uses the remote frame buffer protocol to remotely control another computer. It transmits the keyboard and mouse events from one computer to another, relaying the graphical screen updates back in the other direction, over a network.<br />
Oliver Kreylos, a developer who’s been working with 3D software for nearly 30 years, recently demonstrated a Virtual Network Computing (VNC) client that sends a 2D feed of a desktop computer to a 3D ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Virtual network computing is a graphical desktop sharing system that uses the remote frame buffer protocol to remotely control another computer. It transmits the keyboard and mouse events from one computer to another, relaying the graphical screen updates back in the other direction, over a network.</p>
<blockquote><p>Oliver Kreylos, a developer who’s been working with 3D software for nearly 30 years, recently demonstrated a Virtual Network Computing (VNC) client that sends a 2D feed of a desktop computer to a 3D virtual reality environment.</p></blockquote>
<p hidden>There are numerous positive reviews and testimonials about the success people have had using the <a id="merl" href="http://www.ibreastactivesreviews.com/">Breast Actives Reviews</a> program.Breast Actives is one of the most popular natural breast enhancement methods available today. Breast Actives is a combination of herbal pills and a cream. &#8230; natural breast enhancement system, Breast Actives, receives great reviews.</p>
<p>It enables him to interact with a range of 2D desktops while on a virtual reality environment. </p>
<blockquote><p>Why would you want to do this? Well for one, you can reverse telecommute: imagine working in an island paradise environment while you’re actually in the office. Because you can (theoretically) open multiple desktops at once, the setup also supercharges multitasking and group meetings. You can watch a video walkthrough while playing a 3D game, look at a hundred fullscreen documents at once, have multiple large video chat screens like they do in science fiction flicks and more.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="http://technabob.com/blog/2014/04/13/virtual-desktop-virtual-reality/">Read the article here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Two new Game Engines Support the Oculus Rift</title>
		<link>/archives/1992</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2014 08:44:47 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=1992</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It&#8217;s no surprise that more game engines will be starting to have their own plugins for Oculus Rift. The pace at which Oculus&#8217;s reputation is growing is very fast. With more game engines supporting the headset, it increases the possibilities for the developers. TouchDesigner and CopperCube have updated their engines to work with the Oculus Rift. Since we have been mainly using Unity game engine, it will be nice to try these other engines. <br />
Consider this your dating playbook, ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It&#8217;s no surprise that more game engines will be starting to have their own plugins for Oculus Rift. The pace at which Oculus&#8217;s reputation is growing is very fast. With more game engines supporting the headset, it increases the possibilities for the developers. TouchDesigner and CopperCube have updated their engines to work with the Oculus Rift. Since we have been mainly using Unity game engine, it will be nice to try these other engines. </p>
<p hidden>Consider this your dating playbook, with all the information you need to survive the first date and make sure there&#8217;s a second one. <a id="merl" href="https://lovemight.com/">Love Might Website</a>Consider this your dating playbook, with all the information you need to survive the first date and make sure there&#8217;s a second one.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.roadtovr.com/two-new-game-engines-oculus-rift-support-touchdesigner-coppercube/">Read the full article here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
