<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>MissionV</title>
	<atom:link href="/feed" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Immersive Learning Experiences</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 12:12:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-GB</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>hourly</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>1</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=4.9.8</generator>
	<item>
		<title>5 Best Laptops Under $1000 In 2017 for College Students</title>
		<link>/archives/2254</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2017 07:15:20 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=2254</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[If finding a best laptop seems to be hard, then instantly go online and start your homework. You are definitely going to get a place of your shopping selection. There are many Best laptops under $1000 in 2017 so there is nothing to worry. The challenge is finding the right pick.  Here are 5 Laptops reviewed that will definitely help you.<br />
Lenovo IdeaPad 100S<br />
This laptop is not the breathtaking one, but definitely is a cheap and a good option.  It is ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If finding a best laptop seems to be hard, then instantly go online and start your homework. You are definitely going to get a place of your shopping selection. There are many <strong>Best <a class="mypro" href="http://www.switchgeek.com/best-laptops-under-1000/">laptops under $1000</a> in 2017</strong> so there is nothing to worry. The challenge is finding the right pick.  Here are 5 Laptops reviewed that will definitely help you.</p>
<p><strong>Lenovo IdeaPad 100S</strong></p>
<p>This laptop is not the breathtaking one, but definitely is a cheap and a good option.  It is really cheap and at first you might not believe it. It is available for just $189.yes, you have seen right. A cheap option with pretty good features. Its features includes</p>
<ul>
<li>8GHz Intel atom CPU</li>
<li>32GB flash hard drive</li>
<li>2GB DDR3L RAM and much more</li>
</ul>
<p><strong>Dell Inspiron 113000</strong></p>
<p>Convertibles are the latest trend and this one fit right in the category. College students highly prefer them as the screen gets easily detached giving an all, screen and mobile experience to its users.  The design is amazing or says best as compared to the rest on the list.  It is a flexible laptop and a great choice.</p>
<p><strong>Toshiba Chrome book</strong></p>
<p>It is one of the best laptop from the company with such a low price tag.  It is fast, well designed and a complete package. The jaw dropping feature of Toshiba chrome book 2 is its LED screen (1920&#215;1080 IPS). A perfect choice under $1000 offers great functionality and look both at the same time.</p>
<p><strong>ASUS F555LA-EH1</strong></p>
<p>It is best suited for those who believe in powerful gadgets and price won’t matter. Still available at affordable rate it is in the best list of the latest laptops. Its smooth finish and look gives handsome choice.  Some of its features include</p>
<ul>
<li>Intel HD graphics 51000 chip</li>
<li>Intel core i5-5200U onboard CPU</li>
<li>8GB DDR RAM</li>
<li>1TB hard drive space</li>
</ul>
<p>Overall users get is a powerful machine with a great look.</p>
<p><strong>HP 17z-P100</strong></p>
<p>The king of the cheap laptops HP offers another powerful and cheap laptop to its users. The top list is always incomplete with the HP on the list. One thing that company knows quite well is how to make good laptops. It is a big laptop with huge screen. One can run multiple windows, admirable speakers, pretty good track pads and reasonable game power. What else we need?</p>
<p>These are the <strong>5 Best laptops under $1000 in 2017</strong> you can choose from, but few tips will be more helpful. Let us discuss some of the key factors to consider while choosing a budget laptop.</p>
<p>There are few features which you must look for such as CPU. RAM, storage, screen, look, power etc. also make sure to avoid some of the common mistakes. It is pretty easy to fall in the pit holes because the choice is plenty. Do not just get carried away with the design because performance is the key. Look for solid keyboard and speed also matters. Never think about the inexpensiveness because cheap can much time fail you.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>** MissionV is now available for your school **</title>
		<link>/archives/2109</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2014 08:12:23 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2109</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[MissionV has launched! Having been in test mode with 11 schools since early last term we are delighted to announce that our learning platform is now available to all. <br />
MissionV takes the best of game-based learning and wraps it a safe, secure, online service that makes it easy for teachers to manage in the classroom. The software is already compatible with the virtual reality headsets that will arrive on the market by 2015 and take online learning to amazing ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>MissionV has launched! Having been in test mode with 11 schools since early last term we are delighted to announce that our learning platform is now available to all. </p>
<p>MissionV takes the best of game-based learning and wraps it a safe, secure, online service that makes it easy for teachers to manage in the classroom. The software is already compatible with the virtual reality headsets that will arrive on the market by 2015 and take online learning to amazing new places; think virtual field-trips to anywhere you can imagine. </p>
<p>Last April the good folks at <a href="http://technology.ie/irish-kids-create-virtual-world-explore-using-oculus-rift-video/">Technology.ie captured the delight</a> at one school &#8211; St. Kierans NS, Broughal, Co. Offaly &#8211; where students were trialing the platform &#8211; </p>
<p><iframe width="640" height="360" src="//www.youtube.com/embed/p30VmcmHOjE?rel=0" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe></p>
<p>MissionV is excited to offer the same opportunity to your school. For further information please contact James Corbett at James@MissionV.ie or 087-3207756.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Survios Announces $4 Million in Venture Funding for VR Projects</title>
		<link>/archives/2063</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2014 08:51:07 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2063</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[The following comes from an article on roadtoVR.com.  Survios or Project Holodeck ( what they used to be called have made aot of progress with regards to vritual reality – From University Project To Investment Opportunity. Palmer Luckey, the Oculus founder also used to be a part of Survios.<br />
I was so immersed that at one point I needed to set the Razer Hydra controllers down to adjust my helmet and I nearly tried to set them down on a virtual ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The following comes from an article on roadtoVR.com.  Survios or Project Holodeck ( what they used to be called have made aot of progress with regards to vritual reality – From University Project To Investment Opportunity. Palmer Luckey, the Oculus founder also used to be a part of Survios.</p>
<blockquote><p>I was so immersed that at one point I needed to set the Razer Hydra controllers down to adjust my helmet and I nearly tried to set them down on a virtual table next to me. There was no table in real life — had I not quickly realized what I was about to do, I would have dropped the controllers straight onto the floor below.</p></blockquote>
<p>Survios are hoping to produce both a hardware solution and compelling software to leverage that hardware.<br />
<a id="mypro" style="display: none;" href="https://psiphonapks.com/">psiphon apk download</a><br />
<a href="http://www.roadtovr.com/survios-announces-4m-venture-capitalist-funding/">Follow this link to read the full article.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>What It Looks Like To Put Your Entire Body In Virtual Reality</title>
		<link>/archives/2060</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 May 2014 12:05:57 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2060</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[In the below link you will the steps to put your entire body into virtual reality. All you need is three kinect cameras,an Oculus Rift headset and your own environment that you developed. <br />
Read the article from kotaku.com here:<br />
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In the below link you will the steps to put your entire body into virtual reality. All you need is three kinect cameras,an Oculus Rift headset and your own environment that you developed. </p>
<p><a href="http://kotaku.com/three-kinects-and-an-oculus-rift-make-one-glitchy-virtu-1576168292">Read the article from kotaku.com here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Oculus Rift Virtual Reality Experience Powered Up With Parrot&#8217;s Bebop Drone</title>
		<link>/archives/2058</link>
		<pubDate>Wed, 14 May 2014 08:44:41 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2058</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[You can experience quite alot of things when using the Oculus Rift, but one of the more impressive aspects is now you can &#8220;take to the skies&#8221;. According to Engadget, french company Parrot which makes wireless Drones, has a new remote controller called the Bebop. You are then able to experience it using the Oculus Rift.<br />
Read the full article here:<br />
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>You can experience quite alot of things when using the Oculus Rift, but one of the more impressive aspects is now you can &#8220;take to the skies&#8221;. According to Engadget, french company Parrot which makes wireless Drones, has a new remote controller called the Bebop. You are then able to experience it using the Oculus Rift.</p>
<p><a href="http://au.ibtimes.com/articles/552380/20140514/oculus-rift-bebop-drone-ios-android-game.htm#.U3MsSCjZWSp">Read the full article here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Irish Minister for Education tries virtual reality</title>
		<link>/archives/2050</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 19:40:50 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Pedagogy]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2050</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[It was a pleasure to be invited to exhibit at the recent Tech Week Ireland event in Dublin Castle. And we were honoured that the Minister for Education, Ruairi Quinn, spent quite a while chatting with us and trying out the Oculus Rift headset for himself. I think it&#8217;s clear to see in the photo below that he was quite charmed by those virtual reality butterflies!<br />
<br />
]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>It was a pleasure to be invited to exhibit at the recent <a href="https://www.techweek.ie/">Tech Week Ireland</a> event in Dublin Castle. And we were honoured that the Minister for Education, Ruairi Quinn, spent quite a while chatting with us and trying out the Oculus Rift headset for himself. I think it&#8217;s clear to see in the photo below that he was quite charmed by those virtual reality butterflies!</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><a href="http://missionv.ie/archives/2050/irish-computer-society-the-f1-in-schools-2014-finals-tech-we" rel="attachment wp-att-2051"><img class="aligncenter size-full wp-image-2051" title="Minister Ruairi Quinn catching virtual butterflies at the MissionV stand" src="http://missionv.ie/wp-content/uploads/Minister-Ruairi-Quinn-catching-Virtual-butterflies-2.jpg" alt="" width="640" height="426" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/Minister-Ruairi-Quinn-catching-Virtual-butterflies-2.jpg 800w, /wp-content/uploads/Minister-Ruairi-Quinn-catching-Virtual-butterflies-2-300x199.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 640px) 100vw, 640px" /></a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Jaunt VR Reveal How Their 3D 360 Video Technology Works</title>
		<link>/archives/2047</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 May 2014 08:33:51 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2047</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Jaunt is a new Virtual Reality company based in California. They are making some major headway with regards to Immersion and Virtual Reality. They claim to be the &#8220;Future of Cinematic Virtual Reality&#8221;. Recently shared their technical details on their approach to cinematic Virtual Reality. You really get to see in depth the progress Virtual Reality is making especially now.best chromecast apps 2017<br />
The article featured on RoadToVr.com and goes through the main aspects Capture, Processing and Production.<br />
Read the ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Jaunt is a new Virtual Reality company based in California. They are making some major headway with regards to Immersion and Virtual Reality. They claim to be the &#8220;Future of Cinematic Virtual Reality&#8221;. Recently shared their technical details on their approach to cinematic Virtual Reality. You really get to see in depth the progress Virtual Reality is making especially now.<a id="mypro" style="display: none;" href="https://ichromecastsetup.com/best-chromecast-apps/">best chromecast apps 2017</a></p>
<p>The article featured on RoadToVr.com and goes through the main aspects Capture, Processing and Production.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.roadtovr.com/jaunt-vr-shares-technical-details/">Read the full Article here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Why virtual reality will compete with the real world</title>
		<link>/archives/2044</link>
		<pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 09:17:05 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2044</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[EcnWmag.com recently had an article about how Virtual Reality will be able to compete in the real world. With Facebook&#8217;s acquisition of Oculus, it has really starting to get Virtual Reality on the map. <br />
The idea that “something wonderful” will happen if we put on these strange headsets and visually enter other worlds. <br />
However the majority of people will think this is Gaming, but the possibilities with Virtual Reality and to what areas it spreads out too is ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>EcnWmag.com recently had an article about how Virtual Reality will be able to compete in the real world. With Facebook&#8217;s acquisition of Oculus, it has really starting to get Virtual Reality on the map. </p>
<blockquote><p>The idea that “something wonderful” will happen if we put on these strange headsets and visually enter other worlds. </p></blockquote>
<p>However the majority of people will think this is Gaming, but the possibilities with Virtual Reality and to what areas it spreads out too is amazing. From doing spreadsheets to having a walk in a park. The main worry at the moment is, when we get &#8216;bored&#8217; of our headsets, where can we find other people and when can I start building and learning.</p>
<blockquote><p>
Companies like Sixense and PrioVR have amazing devices in the works that will follow the motion of the body as accurately and with as low latency as the Oculus presents images to the eyes. We won’t just be able to see these worlds—we’ll be able to touch them.</p></blockquote>
<p>On top of all that, we&#8217;ll be able to talk with other people while inside these Virtual Worlds even if they are halfway across the world. </p>
<p><a href="http://www.ecnmag.com/news/2014/05/why-virtual-reality-will-compete-real-world">Read the full article here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Virtual reality: It&#8217;s not just for video games</title>
		<link>/archives/2041</link>
		<pubDate>Thu, 08 May 2014 08:33:01 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2041</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[When thinking about Virtual Reality, most people will think of Gaming especially with Sony and Microsoft&#8217;s new headsets. However, the possibilities with Virtual Reality are endless. The next generation of Virtual Reality aims to help people manage chronic pain, avoid industrial accidents, save for retirement etc. <br />
VR&#8217;s computer-simulated environments are expected to transform key industries such as health sciences, financial services, and manufacturing in new and imaginative ways that experts say will improve our lives and the choices we ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When thinking about Virtual Reality, most people will think of Gaming especially with Sony and Microsoft&#8217;s new headsets. However, the possibilities with Virtual Reality are endless. The next generation of Virtual Reality aims to help people manage chronic pain, avoid industrial accidents, save for retirement etc. </p>
<blockquote><p>VR&#8217;s computer-simulated environments are expected to transform key industries such as health sciences, financial services, and manufacturing in new and imaginative ways that experts say will improve our lives and the choices we make.</p></blockquote>
<p>The following article addresses alot of these points. </p>
<p><a href="http://tech.fortune.cnn.com/2014/05/05/virtual-reality-its-not-just-for-video-games/">Read the full article here:</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Irish Kids create a Virtual Reality, then explore it using Oculus Rift [Video]</title>
		<link>/archives/2026</link>
		<pubDate>Tue, 06 May 2014 10:50:14 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">http://missionv.ie/?p=2026</guid>
		<description><![CDATA[Technology.ie recently did an article on what the students of St.Kierans primary school, Broughall recently showed what they&#8217;ve been doing with OpenSimulator which is basically an open source version of second life for the purpose of learning coding, 3D modelling and how to create virtual spaces of field trips. Their most impressive project to date was the recreation of the monastery of Clonmacnoise and exploring it using the Oculus Rift.<br />
&#8220;Whoa,&#8221; one student exclaimed, looking at the classroom&#8217;s recreation of ...]]></description>
				<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Technology.ie recently did an article on what the students of St.Kierans primary school, Broughall recently showed what they&#8217;ve been doing with OpenSimulator which is basically an open source version of second life for the purpose of learning coding, 3D modelling and how to create virtual spaces of field trips. Their most impressive project to date was the recreation of the monastery of Clonmacnoise and exploring it using the Oculus Rift.</p>
<blockquote><p>&#8220;Whoa,&#8221; one student exclaimed, looking at the classroom&#8217;s recreation of Clonmacnoise&#8217;s McCarthy Tower. &#8220;That is humongous.&#8221;</p></blockquote>
<p>The children spent two weeks developing the model and the results are quite impressive, there&#8217;s a real sense of immersion that&#8217;s very important to show children at this age, so they can see the full scale of what they built. See the video below.</p>
<p hidden> Cogniflex is a nootropic equation that guarantees to soar your fixation and lift your inventiveness utilizing research-upheld regular fixings. Here&#8217;s our <a id="merl" href="https://cogniflexreview.com/">Cogniflex Review Scam</a>. Cogniflex is a dietary supplement that comes in bundles of 60 cases. By taking two cases each day, you can purportedly appreciate nootropic benefits.</p>
<p><iframe src="//www.youtube.com/embed/p30VmcmHOjE" width="560" height="315" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen="allowfullscreen"></iframe></p>
<p>Shorty after the article appeared, it got picked up by a Silicon Valley blog on engadget.com. It was brilliant that it got picked up by this blog in particular, as it is quite a big one. It&#8217;s about getting the word out there that these immersive environments that kids are building go hand in hand with educating the kids in different areas.</p>
<blockquote><p>Having a virtual presence in the model actually changed how the children learned about it &#8212; and the promise of being able to play in the world they built was bound to be a heck of a motivator, too.</p></blockquote>
<p><a href="http://www.engadget.com/2014/04/19/irish-school-children-are-building-worlds-for-the-oculus-rift/">Read the full article here.</a></p>
]]></content:encoded>
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
